Guide to the Jeh Vincent Johnson Papers, 1917-2020 (bulk 1945-2004)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Plans, 1950-2005
  - Multi-Unit Residences, 1950-2003; [58 roll boxes]
    - Church Alliance of Millbrook, Senior Citizen Housing (Millbrook, NY), 1986-2003; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 47-48)
    - Commonwealth Drive Apartments (Wyandanch, NY), 1972; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 132 (Oversize))
    - Culinary Institute of America, New Residence Hall (Hyde Park, NY, undated (Roll Box 46)
    - Dutcher House Apartments (Pawling, NY), 1974-1975; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 49-50)
    - Dutchess Senior Citizens Apartments (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1972; [Over 28-inch roll; 2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 118-119)
    - Ebony Gardens Apartments (Mount Vernon, NY), 1979-1981; [4 boxes] (Roll Boxes 51-54)
    - Gannett House, Hudson River Housing, Inc., 391 Manchester Rd (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1985-1987 (Roll Box 46)
    - Greater Centennial Homes, Greater Centennial AME Zion Church (Mount Vernon, NY), 1971-1972 (Roll Box 55)
    - Greene Avenue Senior Citizens Apartments (Brooklyn, NY), 1972-1979; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 56-57)
    - Harriet Tubman Terrace, AME Zion-Trinity Housing (Poughkeepsie Methodist Housing) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970-1972 (Roll Box 78)
    - Harriet Tubman Terrace, AME Zion-Trinity Housing (Poughkeepsie Methodist Housing) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970-1972; [Over 28-inch roll; 3 boxes] (Roll Boxes 120-122)
    - Harriet Tubman Terrace, AME Zion-Trinity Housing (Poughkeepsie Methodist Housing) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970-1972; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 131 (Oversize))
    - Hillcrest House of Hudson River Housing, Inc., tracings and logs (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1989-1991; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 58-59)
    - Interfaith Towers Senior Citizens Housing (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1979-1980 (Roll Box 60)
    - Interfaith Towers Senior Citizens Housing, Sheets E1-E2 (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1978; [Over 36-inch roll, 2 sheets] (Roll Box 127 (Oversize))
    - Kings Court Apartments, 117 South Second Ave (Mount Vernon, NY), 1977 (Roll Box 61)
    - Lake Street Housing (Newburgh, NY), 1969-1970; [Over 36-inch roll; 3 boxes] (Roll Boxes 134-136 (Oversize))
    - Lake Street Housing - Community Building (Newburgh, NY), 1971 (Roll Box 46)
    - Lakeview Arms Senior Citizen Apartments (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1980 (Roll Box 62)
    - Lakeview Arms Senior Citizen Apartments (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1977-1978; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 125 (Oversize))
    - Maximize Hudson River Properties - 38 Bement St, 277 and 315 Church St (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1981 (Roll Box 63)
    - McQuade Foundation, The Boy's Residences (New Windsor, NY), 1973 (Roll Box 63)
    - Mill Street Apartments (Kerhonkson, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 63)
    - Morissania Town Houses, The Bronx (New York, NY), 1980 (Roll Box 63)
    - Neighborhood Housing Program, Inc., Scattered duplexes (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970-1971 (Roll Box 64)
    - New York State Residence Facility, Putnam County (Kent, NY), 1985 (Roll Box 64)
    - Oakwood School, dormitory alterations (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1982 (Roll Box 64)
    - One Columbia Street Apartments (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1985-1986; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 65-66)
    - Park St Apartments, AME Zion Church (Peekskill, NY), 1971 (Roll Box 64)
    - Proposed Hollows Redevelopment Plan (Yonkers, NY), 1973-1974 (Roll Box 64)
    - Rehabilitation Programs, Inc. - Facilities (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1978-1981 (Roll Box 67)
    - Rehabilitation Programs, Inc. - Residence Cottages #1-3 (Hyde Park, NY), 1979-1980 (Roll Box 67)
    - Rehabilitation Programs, Inc. - Residence Cottages #1-3, site plans (Hyde Park, NY), 1976; [Over 36-inch roll, 2 sheets] (Roll Box 137 (Oversize))
    - Rehabilitation Programs, Inc. - Residence Cottage #2 (Hyde Park, NY), 1979-1980; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 123 (Oversize))
    - Rock Ridge Apartments (FHA Project) (Woonsocket, RI), 1972 (Roll Box 68)
    - Saint Anna Apartments (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1996; [4 boxes] (Roll Boxes 69-72)
    - Saint Anna Apartments, Sheets FP1-FP2 and R1-R3 (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1997; [Over 36-inch roll; 5 sheets] (Roll Box 127 (Oversize))
    - Saint Simeon Apartments I (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970 (Roll Box 73)
    - Saint Simeon Apartments I, site plans (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 137 (Oversize))
    - Saint Simeon Apartments II (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1990; [3 boxes] (Roll Boxes 74-76)
    - SCORE Project - 10 Liberty St (Kingston, NY), 1990-1991 (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - 5 Center St (Kingston, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - 52 Van Buren St (Kingston, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - 56 Van Buren St (Kingston, NY), undated (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - 67 Van Buren St (Kingston, NY), 1991 (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - 74 Franklin St (Kingston, NY), undated (Roll Box 77)
    - Second Baptist Church, Scattered Site Apartments (Coatesville, PA), 1970 (Roll Box 64)
    - Section 8 Housing (Hempstead, NY), 1975-1978 (Roll Box 64)
    - Senior Housing (Highland, NY), 1986 (Roll Box 78)
    - Town Houses, 39-43 Albany St (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1987-1991 (Roll Box 79)
    - [Town Houses, 39-43 Albany St?], J.A.V. land survey (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1986; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 131 (Oversize))
    - UDC Site 116 Apartments (Brooklyn, NY), 1975 (Roll Box 78)
    - Urban Renewal Housing (Atlantic City, NJ), 1971; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 125 (Oversize))
    - Wallace St Apartments (Tuckahoe, NY), 1987 (Roll Box 80)
    - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Manor Apartments (Yonkers, NY), 1972; [5 boxes] (Roll Boxes 81-85)
    - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Manor Apartments (Yonkers, NY), 1972; [Over 36-inch roll, 1 sheet] (Roll Box 137 (Oversize))
    - William W. Smith Apartments (Smith St Apartments) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 64)
    - William M. Smith Apartments (Kilburn, Foote, and Dreyer, Architects) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1950; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 124 (Oversize))
    - Woonsocket Urban Renewal Project (Woonsocket, RI), undated; [Over 36-inch roll, 1 sheet] (Roll Box 137 (Oversize))
  - Single-Family Residences, 1956-2004; [14 roll boxes]
    - Dutchess County House Prototypes, 1988-1989 (Roll Box 87)
    - Residences - 125 South Broadway (Red Hook, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Alexander (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1991 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Ambrose-Verdibello (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1995-1998 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Attar, Mahlie (VC Faculty) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 88)
    - Residences - Bedell, Wallace (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1956 (Roll Box 88)
    - Residences - Berkley (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Bickerstaff (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Bilcheck, John (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Bisceglia (Unionvale, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Burkard, George and Mona (Wappingers Falls, NY), 2002 (Roll Box 88)
    - Residences - Callahan, Marjorie (Pawling, NY), 1977-1979 (Roll Box 88)
    - Residences - Christmas, June and Walter (Kerhonkson, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Christmas, Vincent (Town of Rochester, NY), 2001 (Roll Box 89)
    - Residences - Church, Jennifer (VC Faculty) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1998 (Roll Box 89)
    - Residences - Clement, Stephen (Amenia, NY), 1981 (Roll Box 89)
    - Residences - Clifford, M. C. (Washington, D.C.), 1974 (Roll Box 89)
    - Residences - Constantinople, Anne, 1973 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Crawford, William A. (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1966 (Roll Box 89)
    - Residences - Crow, Todd (VC Faculty) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1987 (Roll Box 90)
    - Residences - Cusimano and Strauss (Leedsville, NY), 1973 (Roll Box 90)
    - Residences - Da Ponte (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1995 (Roll Box 90)
    - Residences - Davis, Richard (Kingston, NY), 1970 (Roll Box 90)
    - Residences - de Cordova, Debbie and Noel, Jr. (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1980-1981 (Roll Box 91)
    - Residences - Dean, Vincent (Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Roll Box 99)
    - Residences - Donald, C.P., undated (Roll Box 91)
    - Residences - Francese, Vincent, 1989 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Gardner, Paul (Pleasant Valley, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 91)
    - Residences - Gesek, Thaddeus and Mary (VC Faculty) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1988 (Roll Box 91)
    - Residences - Gibbs (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2004 (Roll Box 91)
    - Residences - Gifford (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1978 (Roll Box 91)
    - Residences - Gillin, Donald (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1988 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Glasse, John and Louise (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1989 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Glynn, Carolyn (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1987 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Griffin, Thomas and Delencia (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2002 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Graves, Carlie and John McLeary, 160 College Ave (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2003-2004 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Groves, Earl (VC Faculty) (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1975 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Guernsey, Stephen (LaGrange, NY), 1964-1984 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Havelock, 136 Fulton Ave (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1989 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Hentel (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Hill, Dave (West Park, NY), 1966 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Howard, 25 Mayfair Rd (Poughquag, NY), 1978, 2003 (Roll Box 92)
    - Residences - Johnson, Glen (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1974, 1986 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Jones, Elizabeth (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1984 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Kalin, Jesse, 368 Hooker Ave (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1999 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Katz (Fishkill, NY), 1977 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Kim (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1987 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Koempel, 1992 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Krevolin (Clinton, NY), 1983 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Krieger, Carol (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1992 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Lancaster, Douglas (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Levin, Arthur (Pleasant Valley, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Lewis (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Lipschutz, Lewis and Ilse (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1994 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Liu, W. (Highland, NY, undated (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Low, Robert (Poughquag), 1968 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Lunt (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2000 (Roll Box 93)
    - Residences - Martin, Robert (Dover, NY), 1970-1975 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Maya, undated (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Meagher, Henry (Hyde Park, NY), 1992-1998 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - [Merrywood?], 1978 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Miller (Greenwich, CT), 1962 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Morgan, James B. (Fishkill, NY), 1972 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Noakes (Hyde Park, NY), 2003 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Parker, Barrington, Jr. (Larchmont, NY), 1980 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Passa (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1995 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Poole, Howard and Cynthia (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2002 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Porazzi (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2004 (Roll Box 94)
    - Residences - Porter, Alice and Alanson (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1977 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Pride, Clifford, 1979 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Reuben (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1974 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Roberts (Wappingers Falls, NY, undated (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Ronch, Judah (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2002 (Roll Box 100)
    - Residences - Roy, J. L. (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1987 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Rudel, T. R. (West Park, NY), 1978 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Russell (Oak Bluffs, MA), 1990 (Roll Box 95)
    - Residences - Scheer (Millbrook, NY), 1977 (Roll Box 96)
    - Residences - Sherwood (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2003 (Roll Box 96)
    - Residences - Steed, H. J. (East Fishkill, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 96)
    - Residences - Stevens, William and Gwen (VC Faculty) (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1967-1986 (Roll Box 96)
    - Residences - Shaw (Sharon, CT), 1978 (Roll Box 96)
    - Residences - Stewart, W. Lee (Rhinebeck, NY), 1978 (Roll Box 96)
    - Residences - Strong, Ben (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Strothers, Patricia (Fishkill, NY), 1977 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Thomas, Franklin (Clinton, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Thomas, Julian (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1975-1989 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Watson, Louis (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1986 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Whitt (Town of Tivoli, NY), 1988 (Roll Box 98)
    - Residences - Willis, 1978 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Wood, Roy (VC Faculty) (Marlborough, NY), 1988 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Wright, Ann (Sharon, CT), 1976 (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Wright, Herbert, undated (Roll Box 97)
    - Residences - Zimmerman, Leonard (Pleasant Valley, NY), 1979-1985 (Roll Box 97)
    - SCORE Project - 69 Prospect St (Kingston, NY), 1993 (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - 156 Prospect St (Kingston, NY), circa 1991 (Roll Box 77)
  - Vassar College Buildings, 1973-2001; [8 roll boxes]
    - 2500 New Hackensack Rd (formerly 39 New Hackensack Rd) - Annex, 2000 (Roll Box 101)
    - 2500 New Hackensack Rd (formerly 39 New Hackensack Rd) - Poughkeepsie Day School Addition, 1984 (Roll Box 107)
    - Alumnae House, 1973 (Roll Box 102)
    - Boiler House, 1993 (Roll Box 102)
    - Chapel, 1984 (Roll Box 102)
    - Coal Bin Theater (Shiva Theater), 1993 (Roll Box 103)
    - Computer Center, site development, 1992-1993 (Roll Box 104)
    - Ely Hall, 1990 (Roll Box 102)
    - Gazebos, 2001 (Roll Box 102)
    - Good Fellowship House, 1994 (Roll Box 102)
    - Intercultural Center (Jeh V. Johnson ALANA Cultural Center), 1992 May - 1993 Feb (Roll Box 105)
    - Main Building, 1998 (Roll Box 107)
    - Metcalf House, 1996 (Roll Box 107)
    - Murphy Farmhouse Faculty Apartments, 1982-1984 (Roll Box 106)
    - Pump House, 1994 (Roll Box 107)
    - Sanders Classroom, 2000 (Roll Box 107)
    - Sanders Physics, undated (Roll Box 107)
    - Town Houses, undated (Roll Box 108)
    - Warner Home, 1974 (Roll Box 108)
    - Welch House Apartments, 1998 (Roll Box 108)
  - Miscellaneous and Unidentified Buildings, circa 1950s - 1998; [8 roll boxes]
    - 18-20 N. Cherry St (Poughkeepsie, NY?), undated (Roll Box 109)
    - 24-26 S. Clover St (Poughkeepsie, NY?), undated (Roll Box 109)
    - 88 and 593 Main St (Poughkeepsie, NY?), undated (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Beacon, NY, 1969-1995 (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Fishkill, NY, undated (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Highland, NY, 1989-1992 (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Kingston, NY, 1978-1990 (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Poughkeepsie, NY, 1968-1996 (Roll Box 111)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Wappingers Falls, NY, undated (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in New York City, 1968-1987 (Roll Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in New York State, 1970-1991 (Roll Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Maryland, 1968 (Roll Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Ohio, 1991 (Roll Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in Pennsylvania, undated (Roll Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous buildings in unidentified locations, 1971-1998 (Roll Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous plans and sketches, circa 1950s (Roll Box 114)
    - Miscellaneous plans drawn by John Wimmers, 1977-1993; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 126 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous plans drawn by William Gindele, 1961-1978 (Roll Box 115)
    - Unidentified buildings, undated; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 112-113)
    - Unidentified floor plans, 1975; [Over 36-inch roll; 2 sheets] (Roll Box 127 (Oversize))